What are you doing?
My lord, this is the Yangchun wine sent by Duan Yurou
My lord, do you find it sweet?
Sweet
Dear Chen, what brings you here?
It's because you've failed to extract the whereabouts of the Dragon Jade
I've come to interrogate personally
Perfect timing
Bring me the Truth Serum Gu you gave me
Dear Chen
Don't be impatient
The Truth Serum Gu refused to eat these past two days
It hasn't consumed enough blood yet
It can't be used now
Just as well
I had a physician examine Li Zhi'an's pulse
The physician said since Li Zhi'an was previously poisoned
Her constitution is weak
If we use the Truth Serum Gu
And fail to learn the whereabouts of the Li family's Dragon Jade treasure
It would be unfortunate if she died from the poison
So I wanted to ask you, Chen Lang
Is there an antidote for this Truth-Telling Gu?
This Truth-Telling Gu is indeed powerful
Wait
Could he be working with Duan Yurou
to test me?
If she dies, so be it
Why do you care about her?
Zhu Huaichen is coming
That won't do
The Li family's Dragon Jade treasure
is a crucial step for your ascension to the throne
We must ensure absolute success
It's also the only thing Yurou can do for you
Chen Lang, Yurou always wants to do something for you
You don't think I'm being nosy, do you?
You mean well
How could I ever resent you?
Of course
After all, Yurou belongs to Chen Lang
I've heard the Western Border people say
To lift the curse and save the victim
You need a bowl of heart's blood from the one who nurtured the venom
For the curse caster to drink
Then the venom will naturally emerge
Duan Yurou actually managed to send him away
She's clearly worried about Zhu Huaijin
Zhu Huaijin
Are you and Zhu Huaichen conspiring together?
Zhu Huaichen and I are sworn enemies
I vow to kill him in this lifetime
Not only will I kill him
I'll take everything he possesses
Zhu Huaijin
Why are you rebelling against Zhu Huaichen?
For you
For me?
Back then when you bested him before the Emperor
He held a deep grudge
His revenge wasn't just against you
But also for your Li family's Dragon Jade treasure
That's why he married you after blinding you with poison
Such a vicious and narrow-minded man
I actually loved him my whole life
Zhu Huaichen
You deserve to die
Where is the letter from the Western Envoy?
Father Emperor burned it
Burned it
The Emperor of Nanliang actually burned the evidence of his own son's collusion with the enemy
So casually like this
Father wants us to fight among ourselves
To temper each other
In the struggle for imperial power
Without driving either side
To the point of complete exhaustion
He won't help us
No wonder you brothers are each more ruthless than the last
With a father like this
He treats all living beings under heaven as
Chips in your game
If not for him
Perhaps none of this would have happened
Then you staying by my side using his identity
Was it also for the Dragon Jade?
This is what I owe you
What do you owe me?
I owe you
Get away
Would my lord care for another drink?
Who's there?
Don't panic, Princess Consort
I'm the prince's personal guard
The prince is drunk
I'll help him rest